you stop?
Dreaming on!
Whoa!
Are you all right, sir?
How did they capture you?
I was stupid.
All this time I trusted Kyoshiro,
but he stabbed me in the back.
Anyway, what the hell
happened to the tree?
Big Mom!
She started throwing a
fit back in the dome!
And her attack made it
all the way out here?
Well, that's terrifying.
Though she did help me escape.
After all these years, I can't believe
Kyoshiro was one of Odin's retainers.
I don't give a damn about
Wano's history or its future.
Anyone who betrays me will pay.
Shorts!
Yugarra won't take another step!
They're not as tough as they look.
Butcher them!
We will not submit.
Not to you, Karoo, or anyone else!
Bring it on.
Now, we will take care
of the rest. Not yet.
Forget about us.
Dog, cat!
I think we deserve a turn first.
That's right.
Oh, my
god.
Come on, they're fast.
Yaaaaaaaaaahhhhhh!
It's more than just the
Straw Hats down there.
Those are definitely prisoners
from Udon, my prisoners.
Even Hyogro's here.
Step away for a second,
it all goes to hell.
What happened at the labor camp?
Baba Nico wouldn't betray me, right?
This is the Chief Warden.
It seems we finally got through.
All of our enemies are
sitting quietly behind bars.
That includes Straw Hat, Luffy,
Captain Kidd, and all the other rebels.
I just called to let you
know that all is well.
It just doesn't add up.
Don't worry, I won't blame you for this.
I know who you are after all.
You're an idiot.
You were doing so well
till you hit the last part.
Your antics aside, we need to
settle this situation immediately.
Whatever—stop bossing me around!
Hey
Straw Hat—eat shit!
The island is in chaos from top to bottom.
Hawkins, you only joined the beast pirates
because the situation forced you to.
Now's your chance for revenge.
You're telling me to betray Kaido.
Don't take me for a fool.
One percent—what have you
been trying so hard to protect
the probability that a certain
man survives the night?
Just one percent—I pity him.
Can you hear me,
Toby Rope? I'm busy.
What do
you want, king?
I'm sure you're aware of
the current situation.
It doesn't reflect well on us.
We're gathered today
for the fire festival,
but even with all our forces here we
still allow the samurai to invade.
This is without a doubt the biggest
error in Onigashima's history.
We must put aside
our internal strife even if Kaido
was the one who encouraged it.
I don't get it.
I'm referring to the
promise he made right now.
I'm sure you're searching for
young master Yamato hoping to earn
the right to challenge one of the
lead performers for their position.
I was looking forward to it myself,
but we must postpone that for now.
What you cheater—you had no choice.
Look around, sis—it's madness.
Oh, Pei—Pei!
I was hoping you'd pop up.
Yamato climbed over a wall and got away,
so I need you to carry me on your back now.
How dare you shut up!
back now how dare you
shut up You stupid brats.
Who are you calling the brats?
Don't bump me together
without the odds of a joke.
Kaido is fighting on the rooftop.
Right now, the enemy is trying
to reach the top from the inside.
Move quickly.
Stop them dead in their tracks.
We have 30,000 troops.
They only have 5,000.
We should be able to overwhelm the enemy.
But that doesn't mean you
should underestimate them.
Good luck.
Hey Drake.
We can take advantage of this mess.
Come with me.
I got a plan, but I can't do it alone.
You care to elaborate first?
I have somebody that I want to kill.
We're taking out Queen.
Don't get me involved in
your petty little rivalry.
We can't afford to diminish our forces.
We'll be much better off without him.
I don't know about this.
Don't worry, Sir Luffy!
Keep aiming for the top!
Our men will clear the way for you! Yeah!
So save your strength!
You're gonna need it soon enough!
Forward!
Open up a path for the Straw Hat Dream!
We're not losing to criminal scum!
This is certainly chaotic.
We gotta kick that big boy out of the way!
It's hard to believe
such a thing even exists.
Don't be intimidated!
Attack its feet!
We'll bring it to the ground!
Don't worry, I've got you there.
It's Jimmy!
Bring it!
Come on!
All right, fleabags.
You've had enough fun.
Kaido.
Jack is one of our lead performers.
I handpicked him myself.
You really think I'm gonna sit back and
watch one of my most
valued men get butchered?
I failed your command.
I have no excuse.
Take heart, Jack.
You didn't lose because you're weak.
They're just strong.
Overwhelmingly so.
Their Suolong power has caused our crew
grievous losses, but look at them now.
Look at how many minks you've destroyed.
Get yourself patched up.
You've done enough.
What the hell is going on here?
You know what you did, so
why don't you tell the class?
For one back in the capital, you
let Trafalgar law escape a guard!
Overheard you—I'm not surprised.
It was you, but I can't
determine your goal.
It seems so pointless—I get it now.
So when you said you wanted to kill
somebody, it was obviously you.
A shame that one of our
head officers was a rat!
a rat
Surely you can't be working alone.
You must be feeding intel to someone.
What's your mission?
Who are you really?
It's over.
I can't talk my way out of this.
Kill me if you want to.
But I will never tell
you bastards the truth.
I won't kill you.
Why would I do that when I
could torture you instead?
Oh, the fun we'll have together, Drake.
He's not so big.
What are you doing?
He's as big and mean as Orz.
That fight wasn't easy.
In fact, it took all our power
combined to knock him out.
Not this time!
Lock me!
Loopy!
Wa-choo!
Boy here!
Fountain Man!
Oh, that bower!
He looks just like the
God of Fire himself!
Wa-choo!
All right, fine.
Aw, here I was hoping
you'd put up a fight.
It's more fun that way.
Here you go. Huh?
Consider this a parting gift.
Bye-bye.
Aw, shit.
Fine. But now what?
Can't go back to the Navy.
No.
Figure that out later.
I can't give up.
There's still hope.
No! Stop! Stop!
Get out of my way! Gecko!
Whoa!
Hold on!
It's Drake from the Toby Robo!
Why's that guy helping out Luffy?
Don't give up.
Not yet.
I'm telling you, Luffy's the best.
Strahag Luffy, I can't explain
now, but I am an army of one!
Let me help!
Let me fight beside you!
I'm not your enemy!
seems kind of suspect why the sudden
change of heart huh not to mention
this guy's a perv this creep spied
on nami and robin taking a bath
back in the flower capital wait
what happened looks like he became
half dinosaur seems to be a signature
power among the toby Rope Oh,
but something isn't right.
Has he lost his frickin' mind?
Hey, Drake, what gives?
Why'd you attack one of the numbers?
I'm telling you, Luffy's the best.
I don't exactly know how to put it.
It's like, if he's your friend, he
feels closer than anything in the world.
But if he's your enemy,
he's totally out of reach.
He's more than a pirate.
There's no one else like him.
What does that even mean?
There's just something about him.
He has this power that draws everyone in.
I think I know you.
Why do you want to take down Kaido?
I can't tell you why, but I
assure you, our goals align.
Whatever you want from us, we're too
late in the game to deal with this crap.
Luffy!
You know what he's done, right?
This guy is Kaido's
lackey, just like Hawkins.
Listen, I left that position
and they want me dead.
Oh, so now you want our protection?
I don't want backstabbers
anywhere near my captain.
Luffy doesn't need your
help, so stay away.
Even among fellow pirates,
there's still a code of honor.
Okay, Drake, you can help.
Luffy, no!
I know you're the captain,
but stay the hell out of this!
You must get to the roof,
Luffy. Now hurry! Thanks, guys.
I'm on it.
Hey, Sanji, let's make
it to the big battle.
Yeah.
I think I figured out who's in charge
of all the samurai and pirates.
It's that Straw Hat guy from before.
Let's go after him.
Let's help Straw Hat.
Do whatever you can to hold them back.
Get out of our way if you
know what's good for you.
I'm gonna smash you ultra-idiots flat!
I know those two jerks!
I fucked them earlier!
Wait a sec...
That's the dinosaur guy from the capital.
Hold on, who's that ultra
cutie there with him?
I'll see to it you don't
get anywhere near, Kaido.
This ends now, straw man!
Special attack, Green Star, go!
Wait for it!
Skullbomb grass!
Papa!
There, answer me!
It's me, Nami!
What the hell is wrong with you?
There's nothing I love
more than stomping lizards!
Okay, I hope you're ready!
Cut that out, you idiot!
Did you call me a lizard?
Stay where you are, unless you want
to be doused and wrecked aside!
Don't hide behind me!
How dare you shoot me?
Which one of you did it? Vice up!
Over here, Papa!
It was that scrawny little tramp!
She's right!
You've met your match!
For I am the Great Lizard Buster Nami!
Better remember my name!
I told you enough!
That wasn't me talking!
But it doesn't matter!
We're already knee-deep in this fight!
Fine.
I'm not scared!
Show me the worst you can do!
Huh?
You know your words don't
match your actions at all!
Like your one to talk!
I won't let you get away!
You're in a deep for hurting Papa!
We're out of here!
Yeah, goodbye!
You'll never take us alive!
Stop coming!
Way to go, Usopp!
You better protect Nami!
Right, let's go.
Kinemon's waiting for us.
Yeah!
You've got to cover your ears, Sanji!
Yeah, all right.
I'm about to drop some
fighting music. Slash!
Learned from last time, huh?
Aren't you clever?
But you know...
You're about to be in for
a bad time you kind of
need that sense of hearing
that bye-bye check it out
Chaka!
Kaku!
It's fun to be out to see
you guys like this right now!
Come on.
What the hell happened here, man?
There was a time when the dead of your
wrecked cities like it weren't no thang!
This pisses me off!
Those weak-sized buzzkills think
they can roll up to our party
and clobber the piss out of you
guys just because you're wasted?!
That's the ultimate diss!
All right, it's time to party.
Hachi!
Have you suffered up yet?
Ha-cha-cha-cha!
There's ten of these guys?
I gotta score some more cola.
With a name like the
numbers, I should have known.
Now, it's a giant, it's time to go.
Show him what happens
when you get in the flow.
Give it up, give it up.
Let's get dumb.
What the hell?
Is he able to command those guys?
He's so annoying. Just ditch him.
There's no time for this.
You have a point. Let's go. Yeah.
You can check my freestyle.
You're in denial.
Yeah, yo.
Hachi gonna make you run eight miles.
I'll give it up, Lopey!
Let's keep ignoring this idiot!
Yeah, sounds like a plan!
Ah-cha!
Ah-cha! Ah-cha!
Ah-cha-cha!
Ha-cha-cha-cha!
Look at how strong he is! Careful.
If he swings him around,
we're surely done for.
Well, this is just great. Hachi!
Hachi!
Listen here.
Run straight out of the dome as
fast as your legs will take you.
If we allow that giant to run wild,
then the samurai won't make
it to the final skirmish.
I'm on it.
Do your best.
Always do.
Acha! Acha! Acha!
General Franky is not your
personal plaything, you big goon.
Acha! Acha!
And good luck trying to catch me.
Oh, damn.
No respect, I tell you.
I'll show him I've got some dumb toy!
At least hear me out!
I have a lot to gain from your victory!
My life depends on it!
How can I convince you?
I gotta admit, you seem
like an honest guy.
But...
There won't be an alliance till
I figure out what makes you tick.
Who are you, what do you
want, and who do you work for?
Rise up!
Bring the party to the scene!
Crankin' number's gonna make you scream!
Come on out! Yoo-hoo!
I need your help!
You sobered up yet?
You better knock that shit off.
I heard some interesting
rumors about you homie.
Let me guess, you're out of options,
so you're leeching off that
weak little pirate crew.
I never liked you, Apu; I've been
waiting for an excuse to kick your ass.
This isn't a favor for Straw
Head; I just hate that guy.
We've got one thing in common at least.
I've got a score to settle
with this clown myself.
Fine, I give in.
It's an alliance.
What did you say?
Oh, Dark!
Now I got you right where I
want you, you traitorous turd.
But you're more than a traitor.
You're a spy.
You're pretty popular.
Sure you want to team up with Luffy?
I never wanted them as friends, so
I'm happy to have them as enemies.
It's all over! Hey!
You gotta stay with me! I'm trying!
It's too much!
Just leave me! You'll be fine!
It's not bad! You're wrong!
It burns!
This isn't good.
I know these bots.
We're in trouble.
Let's see how long you can
survive my attacks, shall we?
One shot and you're dead,
so I'll start running.
The thought of escape
never occurred to me.
Black friend!
Black fire style!
Black!
You thought we'd run?
What do you take us for?
No more.
We're done fleeing.
The time to fight is now.
We stand here as Lord Odin's samurai
and we shall proudly die as such.
After relieving you of your head, that is!